Guide to the Walter E. Fauntroy papers, 1941-1990 MS2070
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Affiliations and organization files, 1940-1989; MS2070 Series 2; 6 Linear feet
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Correspondence, George Grier, 1967 September 06 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Correspondence, Thomas Appleby, 1967-1968 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Correspondence, Samuel Armstrong, 1967 November 01 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Correspondence, Ester Croon, 1967 November 27 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Correspondence, Robert Weaver, 1967 December 02 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Correspondence, Reginald Griffith, 1968-1971 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Correspondence, Roy Littlejohn, 1968 April (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Correspondence, James Lancaster, 1968 July 09 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Correspondence, James Kunen, 1968 July 10 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Correspondence, Robert Rauner, 1968 August 09 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Correspondence, Marcia Kunen, 1968 August 12 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Correspondence, Walter Washington, 1968 August 15-26 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Correspondence, John Fairfax, 1968 August 21 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Correspondence, Daniel Moyihan, 1969 March 13 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Correspondence, Robert Goostree, 1969 March 18 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Correspondence, Frank Del Vecchio, 1969 March 25 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Correspondence, William Derrick, 1969 July 03 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Correspondence, Henry Silva, 1969 September 23 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Correspondence, James Woolfolk, 1971 June-1971 July (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Correspondence, David Apter, 1971 June 30 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Correspondence, William Stewart, 1971 June 30-November (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Correspondence, Melvin Mister, 1971 July 12-August 13 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Correspondence, Donald Yancey, 1971 July 30 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Correspondence, Lloyd Elliott, 1971 September 27 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Correspondence, Board Members, 1971 October 04 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Correspondence, D.C. Redevelopment Land Agency, 1971-1974 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Correspondence, MICCO and RLA, 1973 January (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Correspondence, Paul Moore, undated (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Flyer, "Tell It Like It Is", 1967 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Handbook, MICCO Personnel Handbook and Roster, Circa 1971 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Meeting Files, Board Members, 1968-1971 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Meeting Files, Nominating Committee 5th Annual Report, 1971 January 30 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Meeting Files, Housing Committee, 1971 May 04 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Meeting Files, MICCO Minutes, 1971 June 24 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Newsletters, "Shaw Power", 1969-1971 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Package, MICCO Industries Recapitalization, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Pamphlet, "Shaw School Sites", Circa 1970 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Pamphlet, "2nd Action Year for Shaw", undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Pamphlet, "MICCO Shaw Urban Renewal and You", undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Plan, MICCO- RLA Parcels in Shaw, 1971 June 12 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Plan, 3rd Year Action Sites, undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Proposal, Inner City Planning Associates, 1969-1970 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Proposal, Education and Training, undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Questionnaire, MICCO Community Results, Circa 1968 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Report, MICCO Program Development, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Report, Annual Report, 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Report, Annual Report, 1968-1969 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Report, Annual Report, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Report, First Action Year, Circa 1968 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Report, Educational Committee, Circa 1971 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Report, Rehab Properties, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Report, Sure Reports, 1971 May 17 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Song, MICCO Theme Song, Circa 1971 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Statement, National Capital Planning Commission, 1966 April 07 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Statement, MICCO and the National Transportation Agency, 1967 March 22 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Statement, 2nd Urban Renewal Action Year, 1970 June 30 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Statement, USURY Laws, Circa 1970 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Statement, Lincoln-Westmoreland Apartments, 1971 May 27 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Statement, 3rd Year Action Sites and Programs, 1971 August 09 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Model Inner City Community Organization (MICCO): Transcript, Black Power, 1968 August 22-23 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - New Birth Corporation, Inc.: Clipping, Daytona Times, "Howard Thurman Religious Resource Center", 1967 November 26-December 02 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - New Birth Corporation, Inc.: Correspondence, Fund Raising Campaign, undated (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - New Birth Corporation, Inc.: Meeting Files, New Birth Workshop Outline, 1986 January 04-06 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - New Birth Corporation, Inc.: Meeting Files, Board of Trustees, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Shaw Urban Renewal: Announcement, Thanksgiving Concert, undated (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Shaw Urban Renewal: Booklet, Shaw Construction Goals, 1971 July-1972 September (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Shaw Urban Renewal: Booklet, A Program for Bates Street, 1973 February (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Shaw Urban Renewal: Booklet, Proposed Modifications, 1973 February (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Shaw Urban Renewal: Booklet, "What Kind of Neighborhood Do You Want?", undated (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Shaw Urban Renewal: Brochure, "The New Shaw School and You" and A Guide to Churches & Institutions in the Shaw Urban Renewal Area, Circa 1970 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Shaw Urban Renewal: Clippings, Shaw Urban Renewal Area, 1960-1972 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Shaw Urban Renewal: Correspondence, Beatrice Coleman, 1972 June 14 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Shaw Urban Renewal: Correspondence, Jeffrey Cohen, 1989 August 17 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Shaw Urban Renewal: Flyers, The Shaw Plan, 1970 February 12 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Shaw Urban Renewal: Map, Shaw School Urban Renewal Area, undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Shaw Urban Renewal: Newsletter, Shaw Merchants, Circa 1990 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Shaw Urban Renewal: Pamphlet, "What' s Happening at 7th and R in Shaw", Circa 1970 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Shaw Urban Renewal: Plan, The Shaw Urban Renewal Area, Circa 1969 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Shaw Urban Renewal: Plan, Shaw School Urban Renewal Plan, Circa 1971 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Shaw Urban Renewal: Presentation "We Did It Before and We Ca It Again,", 1989 October 04 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Shaw Urban Renewal: Program, Apartment Dedication, 1975 November 15 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Shaw Urban Renewal: Proposal, "Shaw Area Restoration Joint Venture", 1976 February (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Shaw Urban Renewal: Report, Annual Report, "Shaw Urban Renewal Area", 1970 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Shaw Urban Renewal: Resolution, "The Shaw School Urban Renewal Area", 1971 July 01 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Shaw Urban Renewal: Statement, Housing and Urbavelopment Committee, 1971 August 09 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Shaw Urban Renewal: Transcript, The Shaw Plan, undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Constitution and By-laws, SCLC, undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Article, "Fumbling on the New Frontier", 1962 March 03 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Article, "Operation Breadbasket", 1966 December 29 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Button, "Freedom Now", undated (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Booklet, "Poor Peoples Campaign", 1968 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Campaign Files, "Get Out The Vote", 1962-1964 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Campaign Files, People to People Northern City Tours (Cleveland and Philadelphia), 1965 July-August (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Clippings, Civil Rights Protest, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Clippings, "The Walk to the Ballot Box- The Walk to Freedom..", 1964 November (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Clippings, Selma, Alabama, Circa 1965 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Clippings, Operation Breadbasket Seminar, 1967 April 08 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Clipping, "A Long Way From Canaan", 1973 August 19 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Clippings, "Freedom Train", undated (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Correspondence, Oliver Taylor, 1963 August 28 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Correspondence, Washington Area Clergy, 1963 December 07 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Correspondence, Merlin Myers, 1964 June 02 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Correspondence, S. Kriger, 1965 March 15 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Correspondence, Ralph Abernathy, 1965 May 06-1971 September 14 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Correspondence, M.J. Jones, 1965 June 21 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Correspondence, Hosea Williams, 1965 October 06-1970 August 10 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Correspondence, Charles Lomax, 1965 October 15 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Correspondence, Discrimination in Charleston, SC, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Correspondence, Len, 1969 September 11 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Correspondence, SCLC Staff, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Correspondence, Brad Tyson, 1970 September 01 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Correspondence, Carl Farris, 1971 November 30 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Correspondence, Henry Silva, 1974 March 20 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Correspondence, Joseph Lowery, 1984 January 06 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Correspondence, National Board of Directors, 1988 March (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Flyer, 26th Annual Convention, 1983 August 24-27 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Meeting Files, Executive Staff Minutes, 1969 July 09-22 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Meeting Files, Board of Directors Special Meeting, 1974 February 22 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Meeting Files, National Board, 1974-1988 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Meeting Files, Center for Community Action Education, 1965 August (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Meeting Files, National Conference on Religion and Race Commission on Race and Religion, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Newsletter, SCLC Vol. 1 No. 12, 1963 September (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: News Releases, SCLC, 1962-1979 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: News Releases, SCLC Washington Bureau, 1965-1967 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: News Release, Poor Peoples Campaign, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Pamphlet, Crusade For The Vote, undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Pamphlet, "Sunshine", undated (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Pamphlet, This Is SCLC, undated (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Poem, "There Is A Man", undated (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Presentation, Operation Breadbasket, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Presentation, Student Rally, undated (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Program, Nationwide Pilgrimage to Birmingham, Alabama, undated (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Program, People to People Northern City Tour (Chicago), 1965 July 24-August 04 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Program, Operation Breadbasket, Circa 1966 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Program, "A Day with the Word,", 1974 April 21 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Program, 21st Convention Booklet, 1978 September 10 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Program, Freedom Now SCLC, undated (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Proposal, Washington Metropolitan Bureau of SCLC, 1965 August (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Proposal, Basic Education for Disadvantaged, 1965 December 13 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Proposal, Policy and Program Outlines, Circa 1971 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Proposal, Black Political Technicians, undated (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Report, National Sponsorship Committee Meeting, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Report, Citizenship Education Program, 1965 November 22 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Report, Annual Report, 1967 March (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Report, Poor Peoples Campaign, 1969 July 18 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Statement, Martin Luther King, Jr., 1965 August 05 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Statement, Ralph Abernathy, 1968 October 18 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Statement, Washington Bureau, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Statement, Presentation, "Amoral Forgiveness", 1974 April 04 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Statement, Proposition 14, undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Statement, "Repression", undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Subject Reference Files, Passenger Trains, 1962-1963 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Subject Reference Files, SCLC Organizational Activities, 1963-1964 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Subject Reference Files, SCLC Organizational Activities, 1963-1964 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Subject Reference Files, SCLC Civil and Voting Rights, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Subject Reference Files, SCLC Organizational Activities, 1964-1968 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Subject File, Voting Rights Alabama and Mississippi Campaigns, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference: Subject Reference Files, Poor Peoples Campaign, Circa 1968 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Album and Flyers, March on Washington (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Bulletin, D C. Coordinating Committee (Box 30, Folder 2)
    General note
    Item is missing
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Campaign File, Pledge Card (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Correspondence, Kiplinger Washington Letter, 1963 July 26-August 02 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Correspondence, D.C. Mobilization Committee, 1963 August 21 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Correspondence, Support of March On Washington (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Flyer, March on Washington (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Letterhead, March on Washington (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Manual, Organizing Manual No.2 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Map, March On Washington Area Map (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Meeting Files, D.C. Coordinating Committee, 1963 July-August (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Meeting Files, Supporting Organizations (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: News Release, D.C. Coordinating Committee (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: News Release, NAIRO and Council of Churches National Capital Area (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Program, March on Washington (Box 30, Folder 15)
    Selected items from this folder are described below. Please note that this is not a comprehensive list of the materials within this folder.
  - March on Washington for Jobs and Freedom Lincoln Memorial Program, 1963 August 28 (Box 30, Folder 15 item 1)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Letter and Statement of Purpose (Box 30, Folder 15 item 2)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Proposal, Proposed Program for the March on Washington (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Registration, Facility Registration Form (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Report, D.C. Mobilization Committee (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Address, 20th Anniversary March on Washington, 1983 August 27 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Article, "Free At Last...", 1983 August 27 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Article, "America Marches for Jobs, Peace, and Freedom", 1983 November-December (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Article, "The March on Washington", 1983 October (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Brochure, Donation to the 20th Anniversary March On Washington, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Campaign Files, 20th Anniversary March On Washington `I Have A Dream", 1983 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Clippings, 20th Anniversary March On Washington, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Correspondence, 20th Anniversary March On Washington, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Flyer, 20th Anniversary March On Washington, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Manual, 20th Anniversary Organizer's Manual, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Newsletter, "500,000 March On Washington", 1983 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Newsletter, 20th Anniversary Mobilization Committee, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: News Releases, Christmas Call to the Nation, 1982 December 16 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: News Releases, Jobs, Peace and Freedomobile Project, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: News Releases, 20th Anniversary Mobilization Committee, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: News Releases, Support Organizations, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Pamphlet, 20th Anniversary March On Washington, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Preamble, 20th Anniversary Mobilization Committee, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Press Kit, 20th Anniversary March On Washington, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 37)